<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DePaul</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">News</string>
    <string name="about1">
        De Paul School is co-educational institution established and run by De Paul Education of
            Society which is a registered charitable body unde the juridiction of "San Thome Vincentian Society Rewa(M.P)".It is a minority institution and is run in collaboration with Rev. Sisters of Franciscan Clarist Congregation
            ,Noida.The school is named after "St.Vincent De Paul", the patron of the world wide charitable works.His mission and vision
            inspire us to lead thousands from darkness of ignorance to light of knowledge-"THAMASOMA JYOTIRGAMAYA".\n\n
            Status-It is an unaided English Medium school affliated to the CISCE,New Delhi.
    </string>
    <string name="about2">
        AIM OF THE SCHOOL\n
            The school aims at academic excellence, development of skills, and character formation based on the golden percept
            -Service to man is service to God. We train the children to grow into active useful and worthy citizen of the country.
    </string>
    <string name="about3">
        English is the medium of instruction,communication and examination.The curriculum includes English,Hindi,Mathematics,physics,Chemistry etc.
    </string>


    <string name="policy1">
    1.For the smooth running of the school,our primary concern and special attention is to ensure a high
    standard of morality and dicipline among the students.\n\n
    2.Pupils must show gentleness and coutesy to the companions
    .Refined manners,uprightness and self restraint should distinguish every
    student of the school.\n\n
    3.Personal cleaniness in ones whole personality is expected.The uniform
    must be clean and neatly pressed,shoes well polished, finger nails pared and hair combed.
    School uniform is compulsaryon all working days and at the school function and even for special classes.\n\n
    4.Pupils are responsible for the safe custody of the books and belongings.
    Each article should be markedwith ones name and roll number.It is not advisable for the pupil to
    to bring money and other valuables to the school.\n\n
    5.Bullying and use of vulgar language are punishable offence.\n\n
    6.Student are supposed to speak only in Emglish atleast in school campus.\n\n
    7.The pupils ewill see that the class premises is kept clean and tidy.\n\n
    8.Before each terminal exam all dues must be clear.\n\n
    9.The result will not be issued until all the dues are paid in full.\n\n
    10. Any damge to the property will have to be made good. The decisions of the principal regarding the amount finedis final.\n\n
    11.Student should get their Progress Report of Quaterly and Half Yearly exams signed by the parents
    and return within the days of its reciept.\n
</string>


    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="title_activity_curr">Lesson</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">Event</string>
    <string name="title_activity_facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lesson">Curriculum</string>
    <string name="title_activity_photos">Photo Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_policy">Policies</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="title_activity_twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_teacher">Teacher</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_class12">Class 12</string>
    <string name="collapsed">collapsed: %s</string>
    <string name="expanded">expanded: %s</string>
    <string name="arrow_contentDescription">Expand list item arrow</string>

    <!-- Sample Toolbar -->
    <string name="no_animation">No animation</string>
    <string name="spinner_adapter_time_s">1 s</string>
    <string name="spinner_adapter_time_ms">%1$d ms</string>

    <string name="address">
        Dataganj Road, Budaun,UP,India\n
        Pincode:        243601\n
        Phone Number:   05832-224472\n
        Website:        www.depaulbudaun.edu.in\n
        email:          depaulbuduan@gmail.com\n
    </string>
</resources>
